Academics Collection UA004
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Academic, 1856 -- 1996; UA004.001; 8.75 Linear Feet
  - Photographs, 1876 -- 1983; UA004.001.016
    - Commencement, 1968; UA004.001.018.00011 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1970; UA004.001.018.00012 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1971; UA004.001.018.00013 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1972; UA004.001.018.00014 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1973; UA004.001.018.00015 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1974; UA004.001.018.00016 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1975; UA004.001.018.00017 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1976; UA004.001.018.00018 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1977; UA004.001.018.00019 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1978; UA004.001.018.00020 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1979; UA004.001.018.00021 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1981; UA004.001.018.00022 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1982; UA004.001.018.00023 (Box 18)
    - Commencement, 1983; UA004.001.018.00024 (Box 18)